http://www.bmv.dk/privacy-policy

90 years of proven experience
HomepageQualityQuality PolicyCertificates Terms of Sales & Delivery Renewable energyAboutCompetences Company Facts History PartnersContactFind Us Our PartnersJobsUnsolicited Application Application Danish Application English Application German
Cylinder ValvesTechnical Gas ValvesCarbon Dioxide Valves631 - Line valve618 - VIPR Valve618 - Oxygen618 - Inert618 - Acetylene618 - Valve Guard616 - Step Down Valve518 - Improved RPV512 - Off-line valve490 - Chlorine valve452 - In-line valve (17E)451 - In-line valve449 - 30% faster CO2 filling 127126Medical Gas Valves535435127Refrigeration Valves552 - dual phase 552 - with two outlets 543Fire Extinguishing Valves580570 370 Bundle Valves616 - Step Down Valve551 510 Pressure RegulatorsRegulatorsBudget regulators047447Standard regulators554-1554-2554-3High capacity regulators160 555 070 / 071057 / 058457 / 458840 Automatic change-over device056-01056-02056-03056-04PRV744 OPSO858 / 859 865 869 Accessories 872 Carbonater CO2 regulator622 CarbonaterFill ConnectorsFill ConnectorsFill Connectors simple431 Fill Connector 431 Fill Connector Mini Pin Index Fill ConnectorsPin Index Fill ConnectorsAngle Fill Connectors Angle Fill Connector Angle Handwheel DesignAngle/Swivel DesignFill Connector with GaugeFill Connector with GaugeSubcontractor WorkBrassCopperAluminiumAccessories
Home
Products
Cookie and Privacy Policy
1. Owner's Details2. Cookies3. Cookie Lifetime4. How to Delete Cookies5. What Cookies Are Used for on Our Website6. SEEEMS CMS7. Google Analytics8. Who has Access to Our Cookies9. Use of Personal Data10. Contact regarding Personal Data11. Protection of Personal Data
Purpose of using cookies at www.bmv.dk
Internal/1st party cookies
External/3rd party cookies
Technical funktionality
YES
NO
Measuring traffic
YES
YES
Advertising (frequency, uses etc.)
NO
NO
Behavior-based individually tested advertising
NO
NO
1. Owner's DetailsThis website is provided by:Müller Gas Equipment A/S Mommarkvej 7-11, Vollerup DK-6400 Sønderborg Phone: (+45) 73 42 12 12 E-mail: info@bmv.dk
2. Cookieswww.bmv.dk uses cookies for the purposes specified above. Cookies aresmall text files stored in your browser that enable the browser to recogniseyour computer if you visit the website again. Our cookies do not contain anypersonal information or viruses.
3. How Long are Cookies Stored?The lifetime of our cookies varies but does not exceed 10 years. Also, they arerenewed after each visit.
4. How to Delete CookiesDelete Cookies - Internet Explorer: http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookiesDelete Cookies - Mozilla FireFox: https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored
Delete Cookies - Google Chrome: https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en
Delete Cookies - Apple Safari: https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201265
Delete Cookies - Opera: http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/
Delete Cookies - Iphone / iPad: https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201265
Delete Cookies - Android: http://timeread.hubpages.com/hub/How-to-delete-internet-cookies-on-your-Droid-or-any-Android-device
Delete Cookies - Windows Phone: http://www.wingadgetnews.com/delete-internet-cookies-cache-browsing-history-windows-phone-7/
5. What Cookies Are Used for on Our WebsiteCookies are used to create statistics on the number of users and enable us torecognise you if a user visit our website again.
6. SEEEMS CMS (User Settings)www.bmv.dk uses cookies from SEEEMS CMS to recognise you when you use our login feature.7. Google Analytics (Traffic Measuring)www.bmv.dk uses cookies from Google Analytics to measure the traffic at our website.You can opt out of cookies from Google Analytics here: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
8. Who has Access to Our CookiesOnly Müller Gas Equipment A/S and Google have access to our cookies.
9. Use of Personal InformationPersonal information is never given to third parties, unless you have expressly given your permission for this, and we never collect personal data unless you have provided this data by registering, making a purchase or participating in a surveyetc. In these cases we collect data such as name, address, postal code, email, telephone number and your interests.
Personal data is used to carry out the service in connection with which data is collected. The information is also used to gain more knowledge about you and other users of fremtidens-tandlaege.dk. This use can cover surveys and analyses aimedat improving our products, services and technologies, as well as the display of content and advertising adapted to your interests and hobbies.
10. Contact regarding Personal DataIf you would like access to the data registered about you at Müller Gas Equipment A/S, please contact info@bmv.dk or call +45 73 42 12 12. Use the same point of contact if incorrect data has been registered, or if you have any objections. You can also see the data registered on you and you can object against a registration according to the provisions of the Personal Data Act.11. Protection of Personal DataThe Personal Data Act states that your personal data is confidential and must be stored securely. We store your personal data on computers with limited access, which are placed in controlled facilities. Furthermore, our security measures are regularly inspected in order to ensure that our user data is managed responsibly and in accordance with your rights as user. However, we cannot guarantee 100% security of data transfers over the Internet. This means that there can be a risk of others gaining unauthorised access to personal data when data is sent and stored electronically. You submit your personal data at your own risk.
Personal data is deleted or made anonymous once it has fulfilled the purpose for which it has been gathered.The fast development of the Internet means that we might have to change our way of processing personal data. We therefore reserve the right to update and change the current guidelines for use of personal data. If we do this, we will of course change the "last updated" date at the bottom of the page. In case of major changes, we will inform you by a visible notification on our website.
To the extent we use your personal data, pursuant to the provisions of the Personal Data Act, you have the right to see which data can be attributed to you. If you find that the information or data stored on you is incorrect or misleading, you can request to have the data corrected, deleted or blocked. You can object to the data being used at any time. You can also retract your consent. You can complain about how your personal data is used and stored. Submit your complaint to the Danish Data Protection Agency, cf. The Personal Data Act, Section 58, paragraph
Müller Gas Equipment A/S · Mommarkvej 7-11, Vollerup · DK-6400 Sønderborg · Tel.: (+45) 73 42 12 12 · info@bmv.dk;
Green hosting service
SitemapPrivacy policyLogin
